{"data":[{"question":"This river is 80 metres wide, but ______ is it?","a":"what long","b":"how long","c":"how much long","d":"what length","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Number + unit + high: to express how length something is ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"One yard is about _______ centimetres.","a":"91","b":"901","c":"9","d":"0.9","answer":"1","explain":"\n-1 yard: 3 feet, or 36 inches (0.9144 meter). ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"A person that is 6 ft. tall in Great Britain, in Spain is _______ metres.","a":"1.5","b":"1.6","c":"1.7","d":"1.82","answer":"4","explain":"\n- 1 foot = 30.48 centimeters","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"This is a ______ street.","a":"one-way","b":"way","c":"two ways","d":"one","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Half an inch is 4 ______.","a":"eighths","b":"fifths","c":"tenths","d":"twelfths","answer":"1","explain":"\n- An inch can be, and is, subdivided into: sixty-fourths; thirty-secondths; sixteenths; twelfths; tenths; eighths; quarters; halves","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Three yards will make _______ feet.","a":"9","b":"12","c":"6","d":"16","answer":"1","explain":"-1 yard: 3 feet, or 36 inches (0.9144 meter).","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"This ruler is divided into seven inches. It is ______ ruler.","a":"a seven inch","b":"a seven-inch","c":"one seven-inches","d":"one seven inches","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Which is longer, the yard or the metre?","a":"the same","b":"the yard","c":"the metre","d":"similar","answer":"3","explain":"\n-1 yard: 3 feet, or 36 inches (0.9144 meter). ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Two yards are _______ feet.","a":"3","b":"9","c":"6","d":"12","answer":"3","explain":"\n-1 yard: 3 feet, or 36 inches (0.9144 meter). ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"One inch is divided into _______ eighths.","a":"16","b":"8","c":"10","d":"12","answer":"2","explain":"- An inch is equal to 2.54 centimetres\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}